2012: Supernova is a action, science fiction film
directed by Anthony Fankhauser.
Two hundred years ago a supernova exploded somewhere in the Lyra constellation.
Now the lethal burst of radiation is headed straight for
Earth, and time is swiftly running out.
The only thing standing between humanity and
complete devastation is astrophysicist Dr.
Kelvin (Brian Krause), who heads up a project to save the planet.
Kelvin, played by Brian Krause.
Tina, played by Najarra Townsend.
Laura, played by Heather McComb.
Agent Greene, played by Stephen Blackehart.
NASA Technician, played by Jeff Crabtree.
Captain Henreaux, played by Londale Theus.
2012: Supernova is a 2009 direct-to-video science fiction disaster film directed by Anthony
Fankhauser and starring Brian Krause, Heather McComb, and Najarra Townsend.
It was distributed by The Asylum.
As with the previous film, titled 2012: Doomsday, 2012: Supernova is a mockbuster of
the Roland Emmerich film  2012, which was released a month later.
It is the second film in the Asylum's 2012 trilogy though the
films have nothing to do with one another.
The third film is titled 2012: Ice Age which was released in 2011.
The tone is thought_provoking.